For the Love of Magic
A Witches' Ball is a family, fantasy, science
fiction film directed by Justin G. Dyck.
Every year the Witching World gathers to celebrate the
newly inducted witches into their world.
Beatrix (12) is eager to become part of this world, but when her pending magical status is jeopardized she needs the help
of her furry best friend Muggs (voiced by Joey Fatone) to solve some magical riddles before the big event.
Will Beatrix sink or soar on the night of the Witches' Ball?
Beatrix, played by Morgan Neundorf.
Muggs, played by Joey Fatone.
Brooke, played by Karen Slater.
Jasmine, played by Loukia Ioannou.
Ophelia, played by Madeline Leon.
Trigg, played by Will Ennis.
The Witches of Eastwick is a 1987 American dark fantasy comedy film directed by George Miller
from a screenplay by Michael Cristofer, based on the 1984 novel by John Updike.
It stars Jack Nicholson alongside Cher, Susan Sarandon,
Michelle Pfeiffer, and Veronica Cartwright.
The film follows three best friends who are unaware that they are witches and that their regular meetings have formed an informal coven; the
arrival in town of a mysterious man who starts courting them marks the start of a back-and-forth between him and the three women.
The film was a box office success and received mixed-to-positive reviews from critics, who
praised the performances, especially from Nicholson, but criticized the story.
The tone is thought_provoking.